import { Question } from "../contestantControls";

export const sarkieQuestions: Question[] = [
  {
    id: 211,
    question: "Which villager loves the item ‘Fairy Rose’?",
    options: ["Robin", "Jas", "Jodi"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 212,
    question: "Which festival allows you to enter the grange display competition?",
    options: ["Luau", "Flower Dance", "Stardew Valley Fair"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 213,
    question: "Which mine level first introduces ghosts?",
    options: ["Level 51", "Level 13", "Level 39"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 214,
    question: "Which fish is needed for the Lake Fish bundle in the Community Center?",
    options: ["Catfish", "Bream", "Sturgeon"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 215,
    question: "Who gives you the copper pan?",
    options: ["Linus", "George", "Willy"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 216,
    question: "Which villager teaches you how to craft a flute block?",
    options: ["Robin", "Caroline", "Sandy"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 217,
    question: "What does the Statue of Perfection produce daily?",
    options: ["Cherries", "Iridium Ore", "Oak Resin"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 218,
    question: "Which bundle requires a pomegranate?",
    options: ["Artisan Bundle", "Exotic Foraging Bundle", "Summer Crops Bundle"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 219,
    question: "Which villager loves ‘Pumpkin Pie’?",
    options: ["Alex", "Abigail", "Emily"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 220,
    question: "What is the name of the island introduced in version 1.5?",
    options: ["Star Island", "Fall Island", "Ginger Island"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 221,
    question: "Which one of these items can be traded with the Desert Trader?",
    options: ["Gold", "Omni Geodes", "Copper Ore"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 222,
    question: "Who first developed Stardew Valley solo?",
    options: ["Noah Clarke", "Eric Barone", "Dominic Hayes"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 223,
    question: "What was the original name idea for Stardew Valley?",
    options: ["Maplebrook", "Sprout Valley", "Willow Grove"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 224,
    question: "What year did the development of Stardew Valley start?",
    options: ["2011", "2014", "2016"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 225,
    question: "What Genre of games (on SNES and PS1) inspired Stardew Valley?",
    options: ["Social Simulation", "Harvest moon", "RPG"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  }
];